gigstart.com 2015-05-12

# Gigstart | Privacy Policy

### External Links

This site contains links to other sites. gigstart.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

##### Registration Forms

Our site’s registration form requires members to give us contact information (such as their name and email address).

Contact information from the registration forms is used to create a unique record to identify the user to the system and for sending information to the member, but is not used for any other purpose. We never sell or rent our users’ information. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. This is used for your profiles and is made available to talent buying members for the purpose of contacting you in the event that they would like to make a gig inquiry.

##### Data Retention

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [contact@gigstart.com](mailto:contact@gigstart.com?subject=New%20Request%20from%20Gigstart! "contact@gigstart.com"). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

##### Information Automatically Logged

When you use our services or view content provided by us, we may automatically collect and store certain information in server logs. This may include details of how you used our service such as your internet protocol address, search queries, or cookies that uniquely identify your browser. We use this information to determine how many people visit the site and from where they are referred.

##### Cookies

Our site uses cookies to save unique key information so you don’t have to re-enter your password each time you visit a page on the site. The cookie is session-based (sits in the header information sent to the server) and is destroyed after you close your browser. The cookie neither reads nor writes anything to or from your computer, but cookies must be enabled to use the site as a member.

##### Privacy for Children and Minors

Protecting the privacy of children is important to us. We will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, you are not allowed to become a registered member of Gigstart unless a parent or legal guardian who agrees to be bound by our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use registers you on your behalf. It is important to remember that we cannot always determine that a member is a child under the age of 18. Members under the age of 18 must have written parental consent to release their name or other personal information.

##### Practices of Third Parties

We cannot control, and are not responsible for, any third party’s use of cookies, web beacons or other technology to collect information about an individual. Advertising agencies, advertising networks, and other companies who place advertisements on Websites, email messages and on the Internet may use this or other technology to collect information about you.

##### Notification of Changes to the Privacy Policy

The Privacy Policy may be updated to increase our members’ privacy protection or to improve our information practices. If there are changes made in the future, the changes will not affect information already collected. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be available on this page for members to review. This Privacy Policy is subject to change without notice. Please review this Privacy Policy on this website frequently to look for changes. Your continued membership will signify your unconditional acceptance to the modified terms.

##### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: [contact@gigstart.com](mailto:contact@gigstart.com?subject=New%20Request%20from%20Gigstart! "contact@gigstart.com")

##### Testimonials

We post customer notable quotes on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information such as the customer’s name. We do obtain the customer’s consent prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. This site sends an e&nash;mail to each customer directly to obtain consent to use his/her full name, event type, city, state, and quote for use on our company’s Testimonials page.
